Inventory of the Papers of the Person Family, 1872-2002
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- 1928-2002; n.d. (Box 3, Folder 30-49)
  - (Box 3, Folder 41-49)
    - Unidentified Pictures. (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - Unidentified Pictures. n.d., 1 item. P. (Box 3, Folder 3)
        Photographic print. 5" x 4", black and white, front view of two men watering a lawn from a tanker truck.
      - Unidentified Pictures. n.d., 1 item. P. (Box 3, Folder 3)
        Photographic print. 7" x 5", black and white, front view of a white house with the water tanker truck parked out front.
      - Unidentified Pictures. n.d., 1 item. P. (Box 3, Folder 3)
        Photographic print. 9 1/2" x 7 1/2", black and white, front view of a group of men in suits standing in front of the United Virginia Bank.
    - Maps. (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - Maps. 1940., 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 3)
        Map of Williamsburg, Virginia, from the Chamber of Commerce, with dotes showing all the important buildings in the city, including where people live.
      - Maps. n.d., 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 3)
        Map of downtown Williamsburg in the 20's and 30's, before the restoration, with buildings laid out on it.
- Artifacts., 5 (Box 3-5, Folder box 3, folders 50, 51)
  - 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 50)
    Fan from the Williamsburg Steam Laundry, with a picture of a woman in a dress holding a parrot on the front.
  - 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 50)
    Fan from Person Motor Corporation, with a picture of a young girl and her puppy praying before bed on the front.
  - 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 51)
    Thermometer from Williamsburg Laundry, with the quote "Before We're Satisfied 'It Must Be Right.'"
  - Oversize, 1 item. P. (Box 4)
    [1910s-1920s?]. Panoramic photograph. Black and white, front view of the William and Mary Football team, with construction of buildings in the background.
  - n.d., 1 item. (Box 5)
    Charcoal drawing of a house with people in colonial costume, unknown artist.
- 93 items (Box 7, Folder 1-5)
  - (Box 7, Folder 1 and 5)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - 1 August 1989., 2 items. Nws. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Alumni Gazette. Contains article about William L. Person being elevated to Virginia's ninth circuit court.
      - 1 5 May 1986., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from The Virginia Gazette including Images and captions about the restoration of the Grove house includes a picture of W.L. Person.
      - 1 7 May 1980., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from The Virginia Gazette, the article entitled "Founding fathers love The Colony" about the return of Person to The Colony and their history with The Colony.
      - 1 March 1978., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from The Publick Observer about the "Exalted Order of the Asps" includes a photograph of William L. Person.
      - 1 1 July 1992., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Frontpage article from the Daily Press on Judge William L. Person the rules on documents seized from a local bookstore.
      - 1 3 October 1984., 1 item. 1 NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from the Daily-Press/The Times-Herald, Ruritan Club presentation honor Garland Wooddy with praises sung by Commonwealth Attorney William L. Person.
      - 1 8 June 1984., 2 items. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper front page section Daily Press, "Poyner gets death" Attorney William Person presided over the case acting as the prosecutor putting Syvasky Lafayette Poyner behind bars.
      - 1 2 July 1969., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from the Daily Press, Saying goodbye to the old courthouse and the packing up of it including three pictures one of Commonwealth's Attorney W.L. Person Jr. packing records and books.
      - 1 4 December 1996., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from The Virginia Gazette, an article about the certainty that William Person Jr. will succeed Samuel Powell as circuit judge in Williamsburg.
      - 1 26 February 1997., 2 items. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Front page of The Virginia Gazette, the retirement of Judge William Person from the bench from the 9th Circuit.
      - 1 12 April 1987., 2 items. NwsClp. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping, a reminiscing article about Person's days playing basketball at the College of William and Mary and the fans that filled the stands in Blow hall.
      - 1 24 July 1985., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping, focusing on the Mustang but with mentioning to the Person family who once owned the oldest Ford dealership in Virginia.
      - 1 18 October 2000., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from The Virginia Gazette, an article that mentions how Person Ford is gone in its copy, specifically that Williamsburg is changing.
      - 1 25 January 1995., 2 items. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from the Daily Press, article speaking of Williamsburg Circuit Judge William Person's nomination to the Supreme Court by the Virginia Association of Commonwealth's Attorneys.
      - 1 30 November 1996., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from the Daily Press, article about Circuit Judge William L. Person Jr. retiring from the bench.
      - 1 13 November 1999., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper front page from The Virginia Gazette, featuring retired Judge William L. Person Jr. in photo, who spoke with Justice Sandra Day O'Connor at the dedication of the new Williamsburg-Jamestown Courthouse.
      - 1 24 September 1997., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from The Virginia Gazette, Kiwanis Club awards retired Judge William L. Person Jr. and two others for distinguished leadership and service in the community.
      - 1 n.d., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping, Commonwealth's Attorney William L. Person announces he will seek reelection and run in the Democratic Party primary.
      - 1 2 September 1982., 1 item. NwsClp. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from Daily Press, article discussing how Person's position is a part-time one but with full time hours.
      - 1 n.d., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping about William L. Person being elected president of the Virginia Association of Commonwealth's Attorneys.
      - 1 n.d., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping about students shadowing people within the government. Includes picture of commonwealth's attorney William L. Person Jr. and his shadow Susan Willis.
      - 1 21 March 1987., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from The Virginia Gazette, William L. Person Jr. announces his candidacy for reelection on the Democratic ticket.
      - 1 n.d., 2 items. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping photo with William L. Person Jr. being sworn in as Circuit judge.
      - 1 October 1984., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping, an article including Bruton Heights Prism students at an egg drop, includes Mary Frances Person.
      - 1 n.d., 2 items. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from The Virginia Gazette, William Person making a plea for paying policemen for their time in the courtroom.
      - 1 5 July 1989., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping photo from The Virginia Gazette, William L. Person's Jr. presentation with his robes of office.
      - 1 5 June, 1984., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper front page from the Daily Press, the jury selection to the Poyner trial in which William L. Person is the prosecutor.
      - 1 8 August 1982., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from the Daily Press, a profile on the law community including mention of William L. Person.
      - 1 23 June 1980., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping for the Daily Press, an article on Russ Cottingham who is going to create a document that says "William L. Person Jr. School of Law" because he spent three years studying for the bar in William L. Person's office.
      - 1 26 January 1973., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from The Virginia Gazette, the Matthew Whaley Class of 1952 20th year reunion, including William L. Person.
      - 1 n.d., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping about William L. Person allowing his courtroom be turned into a classroom. Including envelope mailed in.
      - 1 16 November 1983., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping from the Daily-Press/ The Times-Herald, an article about William L. Person and Judge Russell Carneal sharing a good story about the early days in law enforcement with Sheriff Archie Brenegan.
      - 1 n.d., 1 item. NwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Newspaper clipping about the death of Jim Seu.
    - 5, 8 items (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - 5 n.d., 3 copies. P. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Class of [?] graduation picture.
      - 5 n.d., 1 copies. P. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        "Watch the Fords Go By...Person Motor Corp" car in parade.
      - 5 n.d., 1 copy. P. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Picture looking out the window onto the Dealership.
      - 5 n.d., 2 copies. P. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        A house in the snow.
      - 5 1918-1919., 1 item. P. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Basketball team. And three photos on the back
  - 2-4, 42 items (Box 7, Folder 2-4)
    - 2, 14 items (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - 2 2 January 1994., 2pp. CyTD. CyNwsCl. CyNS. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Tributes to Ed Jones '57. Newspaper clipping and note to Billy Person. As well as a note on the reverse side of the clipping from Ron Barnes '52 to Howard [?]. Also attached is an Educational Supplement Resume, Ronald E. Barnes with the reverse side a typed cover letter.
      - 2 13 January 1928., 1 item. TD. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Document from a safety deposit box of 30 shares Capital stock @ $100 a each share in Person Motor Corporation to Alison Person and bond information.
      - 2 27 November 1928., 1 item. TD. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Document from a safety deposit box of 70 shares Capital stock @ $100 a each share in Person Motor Corporation to Hortense Person and bond information.
      - 5 13 January 1928., 1 item. DS. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Stock bond in Person Motor Corporation issued to Alice S. Person holding 30 shares of the Capital Stock.
      - 5 12 October n.y., 2 items. NS. PD. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Personalized note to William Person from Parke Rouse Jr. including the magazine piece spoken of.
      - 5 18 May 1946., 1 item. PLS. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        A letter written to W.L. Person by John L. Byrnes thanking him for payment covering a membership in the Williamsburg Inn Swimming Club. Including list of who is included on ticked list.
      - 5 29 January 1990., 1 item. PLS. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        A letter to Judge William L. Person, Jr. from Susan W. Clarke, Clerk of the Senate, congratulating him on his election as judge of the Ninth Judicial Circuit.
      - 5 11 June 1952., 1 item DS. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Diplomat from the Department of Education to William Lunsford Person, Jr. from the Matthew Whaley School.
      - 5 1950-1951, 1 item. DS. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Certificate from The Virginia High School League awarded to Billy Person in recognition of a district championship in Basketball.
      - 5 1950-1951., 1 item. DS. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Letter Awarded by Matthew Whaley High School certifying that William Person has been awarded the School letter in Basketball and Baseball.
      - 5 1 December 1948., 1 item. DS. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Certificate of appreciation to Email Q. Person for valuable service to the Nation as registrar during the period of registration, August 20, 1948 through September 18, 1948.
      - 5 31 March 1947., 1 item. PDS. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Boy Scout membership card signed by Billy Person, Jr.
      - 5 3 September 1997., 1p. PD. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        The Kiwanogram, the Kiwanis Club of Williamsburg newsletter featuring William L. Person.
    - 3, 19 items (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - 3 2000., 1p. PD. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Message from Cynthia Kimbrough Barlow and Turner Christian Richardson, about the Williamsburg Reunion "40 years or more."
      - 3 n.d., 1p. TDCyS. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        A partial letter written by Carol Marsh about concerning the Williamsburg Reunion.
      - 3 November 2001., 1p. TD. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        A letter from the Reunion Committee to their classmates concerning the upcoming 50th Class Reunion.
      - 3 n.d., 1p. TD. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        List of the Matthew Whaley Class of 1952 including teachers.
      - 3 7 July 2000., 2pp. TD. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        A letter from the Class of 1952 Reunion Committee regarding plans for the upcoming 50th anniversary in 2002, as well as a note about the passing of a classmate.
      - 3 n.d., 2pp. TD. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        From the Reunion Committee a schedule of events to be held on the 19th and 20th of October 2002 as well as the cost.
      - 3 20 May 2002., 1p. 2 items. 2 copies. TDS. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Letter from the Reunion Committee about the upcoming 50th Reunion. Signed by Les Waldron.
      - 3 4 March 2003., 1p. TDS. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Letter from the Reunion Committee about donations that can be made by the class. Signed by Les Waldron. Including picture of the New School Flag on the reverse side of the page including Bill Person.
      - 3 4 March 2003., 1p. TD. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Email from Will Bill Etheridge telling his class about how happy he was to see everyone at the reunion and that it is his birthday.
      - 3 n.d., 2pp. TDS. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Incomplete letter by John Marsh discussing events to be held and committee meetings.
      - 3 14 May 2002., 2pp. TD. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        The Williamsburg Reunion Committee, 2002 Minutes.
      - 3 30 October 1994., 4pp. 2 copies. CyPD. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Williamsburg Reunion Closing Service.
      - 3 3 March 2002., 1p.TD. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Williamsburg Reunion Committee, 2002 Minutes of the March 3 Meeting.
      - 3 n.d., 3pp. 2 copies. TD. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Matthew Whaley Class of 1952 Directory.
      - 3 3 December 2001., 1p. TD. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Williamsburg Reunion Committee, 2002 Minutes for December 3, 2001.
      - 3 n.d., 14pp. TD. CyNwsCl. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Concerning Judge Armistead a collection of a Rough Draft Resolution including emails and corrections as well as the final product and copy of completed Resolution.
    - 4, 8 items (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - 4 2002., 1 item. PV. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        50th year reunion program of Matthew Whaley High School entitled "Memories Class of 1952."
      - 4 14 November 1985., 1 item. PV. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Order of the White Jacket, Inc. Program for the Thirteenth Annual Membership Dinner.
      - 4 10-12 June 1933., 1 item. PV. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        The Senior Class of the College of William and Mary Program of Graduation events and class roll.
      - 4 January 1988., 2 items CyNS. PV. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Order of the White Jacket, membership roster with enclosed with a note signed by the OWJ Administrative Assistant Beth C. Mills.
      - 4 19 and 20 October 2002., 1 item. PV. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Williamsburg Reunion 1962 and Before.
      - 4 October 1976., 1 item. PV. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Some Williamsburg Memories: Consisting of Articles Solicited from the Writers and Printed for the Williamsburg Before 1936 Reunion.
      - 4 20 October 2002., 1 item. PV. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        A Service of Worship, The Williamsburg Reunion.